http://www.samessenger.com/site/privacy.html

Home
O'Rourke Media Group wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information from and about you because we understand you are concerned about your privacy, and we want to maintain your trust. This Privacy Notice discloses the privacy practices of our websites, whether accessed through a computer, tablet, smartphone or other device (individually or collectively, “Device” or “Devices”), and our mobile applications. We believe in your right to know what information is collected during your visit to our websites, mobile sites, mobile applications, and other applications (collectively, "Services"), and to any services that display this notice and how that information is used and safeguarded.This Site is not intended for use by persons located within the European Economic Area (EEA). We do not request or accept personal information concerning or supplied by persons who are located within the EEA at the time they access this Site. If you have accessed this Site from within the EEA, you should immediately discontinue your use. If you have supplied personal information to us in violation of this provision, whether through the registration of new user accounts or otherwise, please contact us at website@orourkemediagroup.com.About Third-Party AdvertisingWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including any Personally-Identifying Information) about your visits to the Website and other websites that are contained in Web Cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Using a tool created by the Network Advertising Initiative, you can opt out of several third-party ad servers’ and networks’ Web Cookies simultaneously. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please follow the following links: http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/, or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.We may allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements, and we may use any of the Non-Personally Identifying Information we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. We do not identify you to the advertiser.
Receive local news in your inbox!
Success! An email has been sent to
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
Messenger Today
Get a selection of the Messenger's best reporting direct to your inbox each and every morning.
Please enter a valid email address.
Sign up
Manage your lists
Most Popular
Paul Michael Cadieux
Here’s a snapshot of where Colchester stands among Chittenden County towns in updated COVID-19 numbers
After a 30-year run, AmCare Ambulance Service being taken over by Maryland-based Butler Medical Transport
Man unconscious in drive thru facing drug charges
Parents Stephanie Gero and Matthew Cushing charged in infant's death
© Copyright 2020 Saint Albans Messenger, 281 North Main Street Saint Albans, VT | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
